Guide to the Women in Communications, Inc. (WICI) Records MC.89
New York University Archives
- Series VI. Publications, 1918-1985; 3.29 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes
  - WICI National Membership Directory, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - WICI National Membership Directory, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - WICI National Membership Directory, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - WICI National Membership Directory, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Theta Sigma Phi New York Chapter Directory, 1954-1960 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Theta Sigma Phi New York Chapter Directory, 1961-1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - NYWICI Membership Directory, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - NYWICI Membership Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - NYWICI Membership Directory, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - NYWICI Membership Directory, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - NYWICI Membership Directory, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Westchester Chapter, WICI, Membership Directory, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Theta Significant News, 1948-1950 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Theta Significance, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Theta Sigma Phi National Newsletter and Annual Report, 1958-1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Theta Sigma Phi National Newsletter, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - WICI Newsletter, 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - WICI National Newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - WICI National Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - WICI National Newsletter, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan Matrix (New York Chapter of Theta Sigma Phi), 1952-1954 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - New York Alumnae Chapter Theta Sigma Phi Newsletters, 1956-1957 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - New York Alumnae Chapter Theta Sigma Phi Newsletter, 1958-1961 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - New York Professional Chapter Theta Sigma Phi Newsletter, 1962-1966 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - New York Professional Chapter Theta Sigma Phi Newsletter, 1967-1969 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - NYWICI Newsletter, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - NYWICI Newsletter, 1974-1977 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - NYWICI Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - NYWICI Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - NYWICI Newsletter, 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Other Chapters' News and Newsletters, 1959-1980 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - PRO/COMM: The Professional Communicator, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - PRO/COMM: The Professional Communicator, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 6, Box 32, Folder 1)
  - PRO/COMM: The Professional Communicator, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)